amarjyot sodhi

Voice and Accent Trainer: Masters in journalism and communication with 3 years experience

Faridabad, Haryana - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/amarjyot-sodhi/ba2e5a3cbaeccdac

To constantly learn, enhance my skills and capabilities to reach higher level of competence

and apply my knowledge and skill to the best of my ability in the interest of the organization.

Accomplishment counts, not the non-executed ideas. So I just constantly execute the ideas in quest for the accomplishment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Associate

Shuttl - Faridabad, Haryana -

September 2017 to May 2018

Query management and outbound sales

Associate

Sutherland - Chennai, Tamil Nadu -

October 2016 to June 2017

- Query Management
- Outbound/Inbound Calling
- Collections
- Customs Documentation work

voice and accent trainer

teleperformance microsoft - Jaipur, Rajasthan -

October 2014 to February 2015

Responsibilities

To train the students on there comm skills and cx handling skill

EDUCATION

masters in journalism and communication in mass comm client servicing

amity - Noida, Uttar Pradesh

2011 to 2013

https://www.indeed.com/r/amarjyot-sodhi/ba2e5a3cbaeccdac?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN